reissonline.com 2011-11-23

# 

**Privacy Statement**

Reiss Ltd and Reiss Retail ("Reiss", "we", "our", "us") Ltd take your privacy very seriously. We work hard to make sure that we only use your information in the ways that you want us to. This privacy statement explains what information we collect on the Reiss website at www.reiss.co.uk, how and when it is collected, what we use it for now and how we will use it in the future. If you have any questions about the way in which your information is being collected or used which are not answered by this privacy statement please contact us at client.care@reiss.co.uk 

As a Reiss subscriber, you will receive fashion update newsletters, special offers, sale promotions and VIP shopping event invitations. We will only ever send you marketing messages that we feel would be of interest to you, if you have chosen to register your details with us. If you decide that you no longer want to receive our emails you can unsubscribe at any time by logging into your account, clicking on email preferences, then un-ticking appropriate boxes and clicking on update. We will never sell your details to an unconnected third party for marketing purposes. 

**HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**

When you place an order with us we collect certain information which is required to allow us to process your transaction. This includes your personal details, order details and details of your address(es). 

We will use this information to process your transaction and despatch your order. We may at times ask for other details, for example product size and category preferences, age and any special dates (such as birthday and anniversary). These details will be used for profiling and marketing purposes. Providing us with this sort of information is entirely voluntary. 

You can choose to sign up for our newsletter and to receive other marketing communications from us. By asking to receive this information you consent to receive marketing communications from us using any contact method which you have provided us with, including by post, email, sms, mms and telephone. 

On occasion we may ask for feedback from you about the usage or services our website provides to help us develop and improve it further. 

For quality control and training purposes, we may monitor or record your communications with us. 

We will keep your information for as long as is reasonably necessary for these purposes. 

**Data Protection**

We agree to at all times comply with the standards, procedures and requirements of UK data protection laws to ensure that the personal information you give us is kept appropriately secure and processed fairly and lawfully. 

We may have to pass your information to countries or jurisdictions which do not provide the same level of data protection as the UK. If we do make such a transfer, however, we will (where necessary) always put a contract in place to ensure that your information is properly protected. 

OTHER PEOPLE WHO MIGHT USE YOUR INFORMATION 

In order to process your order and deliver your purchases to you we may have to pass your information to some of our service providers. This includes the companies who handle our order despatch service and our delivery company. Your contact telephone number will be passed on to our courier company who may contact you by phone or text message in order to update you on the delivery date or time of your order. 

We will only provide these companies with the information which they need to carry out their jobs. They will only be allowed to use your information in the way in which we tell them, and they will not be entitled to use it in their own right. 

We may on occasion notify you by email about changes to our terms and conditions, or other important changes to our website or our service. 

In assessing your request for goods or services, we may use your information for the purposes of the prevention and detection of fraud. We may disclose your address and post code details to check against the IMRG security alert or any other fraud prevention scheme. At all times where we disclose your information for the purposes of fraud prevention it will remain secure. If you believe your details are incorrect you may correct those details by following the procedure below. 

We will not pass your information to any third parties outside of Reiss Limited, except where required to do so as a part of the sale, disposal or transfer of our business. 

UPDATING YOUR PERSONAL DETAILS 

We want to make sure that the information we hold about you is correct and up to date at all times. You can at any time amend or update your information by logging into my account area of the website and amending your details as appropriate. 

You are entitled to ask for a copy of the information we hold about you (for which we may charge a small fee). 

Should you choose to have your name and personal data removed from our database altogether, you can do so by sending an email to client.care@reiss.co.uk or by writing to us at: Reiss data protection officer Reiss building, 12 Picton Place, London W1U 1BW. 

COOKIES 

In order to improve your experience when shopping on the website we use cookies. A cookie is a piece of information our website will place on your computer’s hard drive that can track your movements while you are on the website, it will also recognise you when you visit our website again. 

Cookies are stored in order for us to continually improve our website and provide a better online shopping experience for you. They are mainly used for marketing purposes, but they are also used to tell us what country you are coming from so we can make sure that prices are displayed in the correct currency and pages in the correct language. If you want to delete any cookies that are already on your computer, please refer to the instructions for your file management software to locate the file or directory that stores cookies. 

Information on deleting or controlling cookies is available at www.aboutcookies.org. However, please note that if you disable the use of cookies on your computer, you will not be able to shop on our website. 

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT 

This privacy statement may change and therefore you should review it regularly. We will of course notify you of any changes where we are required to do so. 

YOUR CONSENT 

By visiting <http://www.reissonline.com/> you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this privacy policy and the terms and conditions.
